bloggeristan.com 2014-02-10

# Privacy Policy ~ Bloggeristan

##  Policy Privacy

The **Bloggeristan.com** know how much you care about your privacy. So we created this privacy policy in order to clarify how your information is treated using our application.

###  Information Collected

**Personal Information You Provide to Us:** When you log into the application using your Google account, we collect the following information: name, user ID, user name and profile picture from your Google account. This information may be stored in our database for statistical purposes.

**Information Collected Automatically:** We automatically receive and record information about your browser or mobile platform, IP address, cookie information and the page you requested. These data are treated as non-personal information, except when we are required to act in accordance with any applicable law.

###  Additional information about cookies

Cookies are alphanumeric identifiers that we transfer to your computer or mobile platform via the browser. They allow our system can identify your browser for statistical purposes, persistent sessions, etc.

Some advertisers partners such as Google, use cookies to serve ads based on users' previous visits to the website. With the DART cookie, Google and its partners can serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and/or other sites on the Internet. You can disable the use of advertising cookies sent by third parties by accessing this link.

We use the tool Google Analytics, which uses cookies to collect anonymous information from users for statistical purposes. Google has developed a browser plugin so you can opt out of receiving cookies from Google Analytics.

###  Information Sharing

Under no circumstances sell or rent personal information to third parties individually identifiable.

###  Policy Changes

**Bloggeristan.com** reserves the right to modify all or part of the conditions Privacy Policy if deemed necessary without notice.

###  Contact Us

For issues related to privacy, copyright or policies of the Site, you may contact the responsible   **bloggeristan.com** through Contact[a]bloggeristan.com with relevant title.
